Guide to the Reynolds Price Papers, 1880-2014 RL.01050
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Writings, 1946-2014, undated
  - Scribner's publishing files, 1961-2013, undated
    - Permissions, 1994-1998 (Box 164)
    - Reynolds Price, general, 1999-2002 (Box 164)
    - Proposals - The Gospel According to St.John, 1990 (Box 164)
    - Proposals - A Serious Way of Wondering / Few diary pages, 2001-2005 (Box 164)
    - Proposals - Letter to a Godchild / In Paradise, 2005 (Box 164)
    - Proposals - Midstream, 2011 (Box 165)
    - Proposals - Ardent Spirits, undated (Box 165)
    - Proposals - In Paradise, undated (Box 165)
    - Publicity, 1994-1995 (Box 165)
    - Publicity, 1966-1995 (Box 168)
    - Reviews, 1997-2002 (Box 165)
    - Sales, 1997-1999 (Box 165)
    - Strachan, Pat - freelancer, 1996-1997 (Box 165)
    - Tours, 1992 (Box 165)
    - Philip Roth, Weekend Journal, 2009 (Box 167)
    - Engaged in Writing, undated (Box 350)
      Written by Stephen Spender, others, galley proof
    - Price Portrait, undated (Box 169)
    - Clear Pictures, undated (Box 294, Videotape RL01050-VHS-0032)
    - All Things Considered, 1997 Aug. 11 (Box 292, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0063)
  - Uncollected fiction and nonfiction: articles, essays, journals, poems, reviews, and short stories, 1949-2003, undated
    Materials in this subseries include drafts, proofs, typescripts and fragments of uncollected poetry, fiction, and nonfiction. Some nonfiction materials in this subseries appear to have been gathered by Price and assigned this title in the early 1970s during preparation for his first nonfiction collection, Things Themselves, as some notes and outlines recorded here reflect the final structure of that book. The subseries also contains a mix of titles later collected in A Common Room; uncollected titles that appear in their own named folders elsewhere in the Reynolds Price Papers; and other manuscripts that are unique to this subseries. Further materials reflect drafts and typescripts of uncollected works which are unpublished, or published in short format. Price's early student work from high school through his years at Oxford is included here. The materials are arranged chronologically.
    - Notes and drafts, Proofs, 1949-1990, undated; 10 folders (Box 171)
      Includes revised manuscripts, drafts, proofs, and typescripts of uncollected fiction comprised of short stories, fragments, and notes with titles Theophanies; Back Before Day; the Heart in Dreams; Holy Places; Road; Short Story (untitled); Time Out; Timothy; A Way Back; and, correspondence and application materials for Guggenheim Foundation.
    - Notes and drafts, Proofs, 1950-2003, undated; 46 folders (Box 171)
      Includes revised manuscripts, drafts, proofs, and typescripts of uncollected nonfiction comprised of essays, fragments, and notes with titles An Actual World; An Endless Shadow; At the Brink - John Beerman; A Baker's Dozen of Memorable Poems; Beatrice and Matthew in the Studio by Catherine Doyle; Belief and Doubt; Borrowed Time, Photographs by Caroline Vaughan, preface; Bouquet for Leontyne; Carol Anthony; Child's Reply (or an Earnest Morn); Christmas Food; Criticism of Concept Magazine; Cyber Time draft of The Unbeatable Lightness of Keyboards; Dear Harper: A Letter to a Godchild about God for Forbes; Death and Work: Milton's Epitaphium Damonis; An Entire World; An Epic Venture; Eternity (for Bruce Weber); Eudora Welty: A House Revived; A Family?; Family Stories: The Carters in Plains; The Fetish of the Real; First Loves - a Preface; The First Printing of Place in Fiction; The First Three; First Words; A General Response; A Grounded Life; Grounds to Stand On; and, A Helpful Sight; Imaginative Writing at Duke; In Paradise: a Surmise; and, Interview of Lauritz Melchior.
    - Notes and drafts, Proofs, 1950-2003; 48 folders (Box 172)
      Includes revised manuscripts, drafts, proofs, and typescripts of uncollected nonfiction comprised of essays, fragments, and notes with titles Imaginative Writing at Duke; In Paradise: a Surmise; and, Interview of Lauritz Melchior; Introduction to Song of Solomon by Toni Morrison; Jesus of Nazareth: Then and Now; John Milton; KJV; Larry Kramer's Faggots: an Introduction; Last Week's Sets; Leontyne Price; A Life in Books, and Hereabouts; A Live Book; The Look of Hope; Looking Back on a Talkative Year; A Lucky Choice; The Main Point; Neighbors and Kin; Notes on a Visit to Ethel Waters; Not Forgotten: American Writers Remember the Lives of Literary Mentors, James Dickey, 1923-1997; Oh, Cuisine: a Platonic Restaurant; On rachmaninov; On Stephen Spender; The Only News; Oracles: Six Versions of the Bible; On Teaching: To the Alumni; A Platonic Place; A Poised Girl; Pontius Pilate; Preface for Caroline Vaughan; Preface to Jesus Tales by Romulus Linney; Preface to Bibliography; Prevailing Daylight; The Private Censor; and, Rescued and Strengthened.
    - Notes and drafts, Proofs, 1952-1997, undated; 44 folders (Box 170)
      Includes revised manuscripts, drafts, proofs, typescripts and notebooks of uncollected poems. Some folders include diagrams of poetry. Titles included are After Rimbaud; The Beasts at Evening; Clear Day; A Crazy Thing; Da Unten im Tale; Damon's Epitaph; Du Schlank und Rein...; A Final Stand; For Ross Macdonald; The Fourth Eclogue of Virgil; The Gate at Treves; Gold Day; Honeyed Eyes; A Hymn of Jesus; If by Luck; In Me Death; I.R.D., Leopoldskron I and Leopoldskron II; Lesbian Slanders Me; A Message Detained; Moon Tide; Notes on a novel; Notes on a play; of the Palpable...; The Pirated Heart; Rank Tavern; Solo: To the Moon; Spring Takes the Homeplace, edition published by North Carolina Wesleyan College Press; A Start: Because I Am; Les Stupra XLVII; [Three Poems After Catullus]; To Accompany John Nash's 'The Moat' for R.F.B., page from The Archive; Two Theophanies; Wednesday, June the Sixth, from Lessons Learned; Weeds; You Often Harp; Untitled [Bud's home on its hill...]; Untitled [Caelius, our Lesbian...]; Spanish translations of Price poems for a New York workshop; [Miscellaneous untitled poems]; notebooks entitled Drafts of Poems for dates 1970-1978, 1973-1982, 1973-1985; and, notebook entitled Days and Nights.
    - Notes and drafts, Proofs, 1966-2003, undated; 27 folders (Box 173)
      Includes revised manuscripts, drafts, proofs, and typescripts of uncollected nonfiction comprised of essays, fragments, and notes with titles Reynolds Price: About Himself; St. Paul Departing Caesarea; Sally Mann; Scenes from a Journey; A School for Husbands; Scripture translationa; A Seismic Event; A Serious Moment; The Start of Things; Three Pieces, and a Start, About Race; Two Years Underway: Pages from a Notebook; An Uncharted Storm; A Useful Offer; A Waiting Beauty; Eudora Welty; What Abides; Why I Work; Why Think of College at All? Why Duke?; A Wide Seam of Memory; Your Maiden Aunt by No Means; Short Works; Untitled and/or incomplete - blurbs, fragments, other short pieces; and, Journals and notebooks (bound, loose-leaf).
    - Reynolds Price on Writing in Southern Review, galley proof, 1982 (Box 88)
    - Notes and drafts, Near the Core (Memoir of Israel), 1983; 4 folders (Box 159)
    - Notes and drafts, Near the Core, Near Day, electronic correspondence, 4 items 4 text files; 185 KB (Digital-materials RL01050-SET-0001)
      Drafts, preface and title page for Near the Core, Three weeks in Israel and Palestine. Bibliography compiled by Price, ends with mention of upcoming publishing of A Whole New Life. Also short biography written by Price; Scenario for a play; Notes for a play and various fiction; Draft of script and title page. Letters to John and Julie regarding script.
    - Notes and drafts, 1991 Aug 15 (Box 293, Videotape RL01050-VHS-0006)
      Bruce Weber commercial for Calvin Klein Eternity. Dialogue spoken by the children was written by Reynolds Price.
    - Student Work, 1946-1953 May Sep 30; 40 folders (Box 174)
    - Student Work, 1953 Sep-1958, undated; 35 folders (Box 175)
    - Student Work, 1954 (Box 350)
      Includes the McKeen-Duren family papers.
    - Notes and drafts, electronic documents, 1992-2004, undated; 174 Files 174 MS Word and text files, 8 MB (Digital-materials RL01050-SET-0001)
      Includes fragments and drafts of Price biographies and bibliography; and; essays and short fiction including A Family?; A Final Stand; A Letter Concerning Faith; An Outlaw Christian; A Serious Reply; Child's Reply (or An Earnest Morn); Dream of Teeth; The Family; Hereabouts; F.H. Again; Hymn; In Paradise; Jay Tolson, Pilgrim in the Ruins review; Letters of Katherine Anne Porter review; Life in Books, Hereabouts; Live Book; Lost Room; Main Point; Matchless Light; Milton; Moon Tide; Near Day; Neighbors and Kin; New Year 2001; Notes for a lecture to the Southern Fellowship of Writers; Old Memories; The Only News; Private Censor; Strangest Story; What Abides; and, untitled works.
  - Price writing in serials, 1950-2010, undated
    The Price Writing in Serials subseries includes works by Price published in journals, magazines, and newspapers, and is arranged chronologically.
    - Serials, 1950-2000 Apr; 17 folders (Box 199)
      Price's work included in titles Washington Home; The Arts Journal; New York Times Book Review; Currents; The Independence Weekly; Brightleaf, and Tobacco Road; Stuart Wright items; The Dream of a House; drawings by Price; clippings; scrapbook, and miscellaneous printed material.
    - Serials, 1951 Feb-1963 Summer; 28 folders (Box 176)
      Price's work included in titles North Carolina English Teacher; Creative Writing; The Archive; Postmaster; Encounter; Concept; Best Articles and Stories; Library Journal; The Virginia Quarterly Review; Saturday Review; Harper's Magazine; Country Beautiful; The Critic; Carcanet; Duke Alumni; and, Shenandoah.
    - Serials, 1954-10-01 (Box 168)
      Includes The Archive covers.
    - Serials, 1962 Feb-1969 Jul; 22 folders (Box 196)
      Price's work included in titles Vogue; Herald Tribune; America; About Town; Life; Esquire; New York Times Book Review; Savannah Morning News; Washington Post Book Review; North Carolina Anvil, and World Journal Tribune Book Week.
    - Serials, 1962-1976, undated; 8 folders (Box 200)
      Includes clippings of articles about A Long and Happy Life; The Names and Faces of People; Generous Man; Love and Work; Permanent Errors; Things Themselves; and, The Surface of Earth.
    - Serials, 1963 Fall-1968 Jun; 17 folders (Box 177)
      Includes revised manuscripts, drafts, proofs, typescripts and notebooks of uncollected poems. Some folders include diagrams of poetry. Titles included are After Rimbaud; The Beasts at Evening; Clear Day; A Crazy Thing; Da Unten im Tale; Damon's Epitaph; Du Schlank und Rein...; A Final Stand; For Ross Macdonald; The Fourth Eclogue of Virgil; The Gate at Treves; Gold Day; Honeyed Eyes; A Hymn of Jesus; If by Luck; In Me Death; I.R.D., Leopoldskron I and Leopoldskron II; Lesbia Slanders Me; A Message Detained; Moon Tide; Notes on a novel; Notes on a play; of the Palpable...; The Pirated Heart; Rank Tavern; Solo: To the Moon; Spring Takes the Homeplace, edition published by North Carolina Wesleyan College Press; A Start: Because I Am; Les Stupra XLVII; [Three Poems After Catullus]; To Accompany John Nash's 'The Moat' for R.F.B., page from The Archive; Two Theophanies; Wednesday, June the Sixth, from Lessons Learned; Weeds; You Often Harp; Untitled [Bud's home on its hill...]; Untitled [Caelius, our Lesbia...]; Spanish translations of Price poems for a New York workshop; [Miscellaneous untitled poems]; notebooks entitled Drafts of Poems for dates 1970-1978, 1973-1982, 1973-1985; and, notebook entitled Days and Nights.
    - Serials, 1968 Oct-1970 May; 13 folders (Box 178)
      Price's work included in titles Shenandoah; The Southern Review; The Virginia Quarterly Review; The New Yorker; Druid; Carolina Quarterly; Archiv für das Studium der Neueren Sprachen und Literaturen; Bulletin of Duke University; 20th Century Studies: The treatment of sexual themes in the modern novel; Alice Tully Hall, and Playboy.
    - Serials, 1970 Apr-1981 May; 25 folders (Box 197)
      Price's work included in titles Chronicle; Esquire; New York Times Book Review; Chicago Daily News (Panama); St. Andrew's Newsletter; The New York Review of Books; The Detroit News Magazine; Spectacle; The Leader; Duke Alumni Register; and, the State Magazine.
    - Serials, 1970 Sep-1972; 16 folders (Box 179)
      Price's work included in titles Saturday Review; Time; The Archive; Bulletin of Duke University; Shenandoah; Winged Words; Topic: A Journal of the Liberal Arts; The Furman Magazine; Prose; Saturday Review; The Southern Review; The South Atlantic Quarterly; Ariel; and, Ranam.
    - Serials, 1972-1976 Spring; 20 folders (Box 180)
      Price's work included in titles New American Review; The Trinity Archive; American Review 17; Southern Heritage Society; Esquire; Duke Alumni Register; Southern Voices; Bulletin of Duke University; Harpers; Publishers Weekly; Book-of-the-Month Club News; New Carolinian; The Virginia Quarterly Review; Aeneas; Shenandoah; American Language and Literature; American P.E.N. Newsletter; and, The Archive.
    - Serials, 1976 Spring/Summer-1981 Apr; 23 folders (Box 181)
      Price's work included in titles Antaeus; Randam; Time; Saturday Review; The Sign; The Ole Miss Alumni Review; Duke University Library Newsletter; Poetry; The Massachusetts Review; The Student; The Carolina Quarterly; The New Republic; The Southern Review; The Ontario Review; Kick; and, Faculty Newsletter.
    - Serials, 1981 May-1984 Jan; 19 folders (Box 182)
      Price's work included in titles Tarheel, The Magazine of North Carolina; Bulletin of Duke University; Poetry; American Book Collector; People Weekly; Carolina Country; Centre Piece; South Atlantic Review; The Ontario Review; The Southern Review; The Dial; Chronicles Culture; The Georgia Review; Writers Forum; Southern Living; Current Literature Abroad; and, Geo.
    - Serials, 1981 Jul-1991 Oct; 42 folders (Box 198)
      Price's work included in titles Aperture; Chicago Tribune; The Washington Post Book World; Aeolus; The New York Times Book Review; The Chronicle; Tobacco Road; The Arts Journal; Durham Sun After Hours; R & R; Carillon: The Chronicle Magazine; Tribune Books; Leader Magazine; Duke Dialogue; The LA Times Book Review; Voice Literary Supplement; Roanoke Valley Journal; Harvard University Gazette; Life; The Washington Post Education Review; Falcon's Cry; and, Preview.
    - Serials, 1984 Spring/Summer-1986 Winter/Spring; 15 folders (Box 183)
      Price's work included in titles The Ontario Review; Modern Literature; Poetry; The New Yorker; Tri Quarterly; Shenandoah; Southern Living; The New Yorker; Vanity Fair; Esquire; Duke; People Weekly; and, Newsletters.
    - Serials, 1986-1988 Summer; 19 folders (Box 184)
      Price's work included in titles The Southern Review; Shenandoah; Harper's Bazaar; Tri Quarterly; Listen; Current Biography; Poetry; The Archive; The American Voice; Kentucky Poetry Review; The New Yorker; U.S. News & World Report; Baltimore; Commonweal; Cahill & Company; and, Duke University English Newsletter.
    - Serials, 1988 Winter-1990 Apr; 20 folders (Box 185)
      Price's work included in titles The Southern Quarterly; Duke; Carolina Comments; Booklist; U.S. News & World Report; Curtain Times; American Theatre; Fame; Poetry; English; The Kenyan Review; Mirabella; TriQuarterly; Aperture; Southwest Review; Pembroke Magazine; American Theatre; and, Southpoint.
    - Serials, 1990 May-1990 Dec; 14 folders (Box 186)
      Price's work included in titles Time; The New Yorker; Cross Currents; Southern Humanities Review; Ontario Review; Poetry; The Chattahoochee Review; Southwest Review; The Virginia Quarterly Review; The Paris Review; The Southern Review; Conde Nast Traveler; Esquire; and, Vanity Fair.
    - Serials, 1990 Fall-1991 Spring; 12 folders (Box 187)
      Price's work included in titles Prairie Schooner; Black Warrior Review; The Paris Review; The Southern Review; Crinkum-Crankum; English; The Kenyan Review; Harper's Stagebill; American Short Fiction; New Virginia Review; and, Southern Exposure.
    - Serials, 1991 Summer-1992 Spring; 12 folders (Box 188)
      Price's work included in titles The Sewanee Review; The Chattahoochee Review; Poetry; The Southern Review; The Paris Review; Proceedings American Academy of Arts and Letter; Touchstone; The Arts Journal; Harper's Magazine; American Short Fiction; Duke University LIbraries; and, Story.
    - Serials, 1992 Spring/Summer-1993 Winter; 17 folders (Box 189)
      Price's work included in titles Triangle City Magazine; Davidson Journal; The Nation; Duke Magazine; South Atlantic Quarterly; TriQuarterly; Oxford in America; American Short Fiction; Duke Blue; North Carolina English Teacher; Prairie Schooner; Randolph County Library News; The Chattahoochee Review; The Georgia Review; The Christian Century; and, The Southern Review.
    - Serials, 1993 Winter-1994 Fall; 17 folders (Box 190)
      Price's work included in titles The Carolina Quarterly; American Academy of Arts and Letter; Proceedings American Academy of Arts and Letters; The Bell Ringer; The Living Pulpit; Guideposts; Esquire; Opera New; Time; Journal of the International Association of Physicians in AIDS Care; Carolina Comments; San Francisco Review of Books; Hendrix; Postmaster and the Merton Record; Southern Living; The Christian Century; The American Oxonian; Reckon; Shenandoah; and, Southern Review.
    - Serials, 1994-1995; 21 folders (Box 191)
      Price's work included in titles The Southern Quarterly; American Academy of Arts and Letters; American Theatre; Scribner Magazine; Common Boundary; The Other Side; Southern Review; ASAP Forbes; Duke Libraries; Slovene Studies; New Yorker; Duke English Dpt. Newsletter; Duke Magazine; and, Southern Review.
    - Serials, 1995 Winter/Spring-1997 Nov; 18 folders (Box 192)
      Price's work included in titles Doubletake; American Academy of Arts and Letter; Nashville Life; Duke Magazine; Forbes ASAP; Duke Libraries;Five Points; Drumvoices Revenue; Georgia Review; Vanity Fair; Auburn Review; Time; and, Vanderbilt University Letter.
    - Serials, 1997 Winter-1999 Dec 6; 18 folders (Box 193)
      Price's work included in titles Time; Metro; Proceedings American Academy of Arts and Letters; Towerview; Mental Floss; W$L Magazine; The Letter Exchange; Christianity Today; Duke Magazine; NC Humanities; Cathedral Age; Forbes; Duke Libraries Annual Report; Proceedings American Academy of Arts and Letters; SLI; Commonwealth; and, Bomb.
    - Serials, 1999 Dec 6-2002 Summer; 22 folders (Box 194)
      Price's work included in titles The American Oxonian; The Art of Living; North Carolina Humanities; Five Points; Tattler; Proceedings American Academy of Arts and Letters; Towerview; English at Duke; Entertainment Weekly; Towerview; Southern Cultures; Duke Magazine; Auburn Views; and, Brogue.
    - Serials, 2002 Fall-2010, undated; 15 folders (Box 195)
      Price's work included in titles The American Oxonian; North Carolina Humanities; Five Points; Tattler; Proceedings American Academy of Arts and Letters; Towerview; English at Duke; Entertainment Weekly; Southern Cultures; Duke Magazine; Auburn Views; Brogue; and, Garden and Gun.
  - Reviews by Price, 1961-2001, undated
    Included in this subseries are reviews written by Price about work by others and is arranged chronologically.
    - Article on The Archive Literary Festival, 1961-05-01 (Box 168)
      This review was published in the Duke Alumni Register, where Price was a visiting critic.
    - Best American Short Stories 1979, 1979 Sep 17, undated (Box 234)
      Best American Short Stories of 1979
    - Blotner, Joseph, undated (Box 234)
      Faulkner: A Biography
    - Bruccoli, Matthew, 1975-09-25 (Box 234)
      The O'Hara Concern: A Biography of John O'Hara
    - Buechner, Frederick, undated (Box 234)
      The Sacred Journey
    - Campbell, Will D., undated (Box 234)
      The Glad River, typescript
    - Clifton, Lucille, 1975, undated (Box 234)
      Generations: A Memoir, manuscript and typescript
    - Coles, Robert, 1999 (Box 234)
      The Secular Mind, proof
    - Davies, Robertson, undated (Box 234)
      The Rebel Angels
    - Dunbar, Anthony, 1969 (Box 234)
      The Will to Survive
    - Farrar, Percy, 1977 (Box 234)
      Straus and Giroux, Lancelot
    - Faulkner, William, undated (Box 234)
      Glands in the Dust
    - Gaines, Ernest J., undated (Box 234)
      A Gathering of Old Men
    - Gould, John A., undated (Box 234)
      The Withering Child
    - Gray, Francine du Plessix, 1981 (Box 234)
      World Without End
    - Greene, Graham, undated (Box 234)
      The Honorary Consul, and Collected Stories
    - Grimsley, Jim, 1997 (Box 234)
      The Lizard of Tarsus, typescript
    - Helprin, Mark and Elizabeth Spencer, undated (Box 234)
      Short Story Collections
    - Hemingway, Gregory, undated (Box 234)
      Papa: A Personal Memoir
    - Humphrey, William, 1977 May 2-3 (Box 234)
      Farther Off from Heaven, manuscript
    - Lattimore, Richard, undated (Box 234)
      Acts and Letters of the Apostles
    - Lattimore, Richard, 1973 (Box 234)
      The Four Gospels and the Revelation
    - Lopez, Enrique Hank, 1981 (Box 234)
      Conversations with Katherine Anne Porter
    - Mailer, Norman, undated (Box 234)
      The Gospel According to the Son
    - Moody, Anne, undated (Box 234)
      Mr. Death: Four Stones
    - Morrison, Toni, 1977 (Box 234)
      Song of Solomon
    - Oates, Joyce Carol and Ravenel Shannon, 1979 (Box 234)
      The Best American Short Stories
    - Percy, Walker, 1977 (Box 234)
      Lancelot, manuscript
    - Percy, Walker, 1971, undated (Box 234)
      Love in the Ruins
    - Price, Leontyne, undated (Box 234)
      The Voice of a Rose
    - Pritchett, V. S., undated (Box 234)
      Collected Stories
    - Rorem, Ned, 1978 (Box 234)
      Aqua Fortis
    - Salter, James, 2006 (Box 234)
      A Splendid Service: James Salter's A Sport and a Pastime
    - Sherman, Alexi, undated (Box 234)
      The Lone Ranger and Tonto Fistfight in Heaven
    - Tolson, Jay, undated (Box 234)
      Pilgrim in the Ruins: A Life of Walker Percy
    - Tolson, Jay, undated; 1 Files 1 MS Word file; 7 KB (Digital-materials RL01050-SET-0001)
    - Trevor, William, undated (Box 234)
      The Collected Stories
    - Welch, James, with Paul Steckler, undated (Box 234)
      Killing Custer
    - Welch, James, 1974, undated (Box 234)
      Winter in the Blood
    - Bayley, Isabel, undated; 1 Files 1 MS Word file; 12 KB (Digital-materials RL01050-SET-0001)
      Letters of Katherine Anne Porter
  - Speeches and addresses, 1957-2007, undated
    This subseries includes drafts; typescripts; and, published versions of speeches and addresses written and given by Price, and is arranged chronologically.
    - Blackburn, William, senior class banquet, Woman's College, 1957 May 15 (Box 235)
    - Untitled speeches, 1963-1969 (Box 235)
    - The Thing Itself, Duke University, 1966 (Box 235)
    - The Writer's Role, Twelfth Annual North Carolina Literary Forum, 1967 Mar 16 (Box 235)
    - Introduction for prose readings, Library of Congress, 1968 Mar (Box 235)
    - Belhaven College, Jackson, Mississippi, 1970 Feb (Box 235)
    - William Blackburn eulogy, 1972 Dec 8 (Box 235)
    - Lecture for the Baylor School, 1973 Apr 22 (Box 235)
    - Knowles, John, introduction for, 1973 Oct 28 (Box 235)
    - Welty, Eudora, introduction for, 1974 Oct 16 (Box 235)
    - Modaressi, Anne Tyler, introduction for, 1974 Nov 13 (Box 235)
    - Campus Club Lecture Series, Duke University, 1975 Jan 15 (Box 235)
    - Peacock, Phyllis, introduction for, 1975 May 7 (Box 235)